// trivia questions from http://www.funtrivia.com //
var trivia = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'The superhero Batman uses many technological gadgets to' + 
            ' fight crime. Which of the following does Batman NOT use?',
      answers: ['The Batplane', 'The Batmobile', 'A Utility Belt',
            'Power Ring'],
      correctAnswer: 'Power Ring'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which one of the following villains is NOT commonly' + 
            ' recognized as a foe of Supermans?',
      answers: ['Dr Doom', 'Lizard', 'Venom', 'Green Goblin'],
      correctAnswer: 'Dr Doom'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following is a foe of Super Chicken?',
      answers: ['The Fly', 'The Zipper', 'The Frog',
                'The Talon'],
      correctAnswer: 'The Zipper'
    },
    {
      question: 'Name the secret identity The Shadow is best known by?',
      answers: ['Bruce Wayne', 'Peter Parker', 'Lamont Cranston',
                'Clark Kent'],
      correctAnswer: 'Lamont Cranston'
    },
    {
      question: 'This billionaire was a New York celebrity and developer of' + 
            ' nuclear weapons. Which of these was the hero that developed' + 
            ' a suit of armor to keep himself alive?',
      answers: ['Blue Shield', 'Iron Man', 'Microchip', 'Dark Phoenix'],
      correctAnswer: 'Iron Man'
    },
    {
      question: 'Deep in the alleys of New York City, Hells Kitchen was home' + 
            ' to this hero for many years. Which of these heroes was blinded' + 
            ' by a radioactive substance that also gave him superpowers?',
      answers: ['Daredevil', 'Black Widow', 'Storm', 'Bloodstorm'],
      correctAnswer: 'Daredevil'
    },
    {
      question: 'Wrecked buildings, craters, total chaos- just a normal day in New' +  
            ' York if the angry green goliath (and scientist in other times!),' + 
            ' ___ is around.',
      answers: ['Thor', 'Vision', 'Kermit the Frog', 'Hulk'],
      correctAnswer: 'Hulk'
    },  
    {
      question: 'What was the name of Mighty Mouses girl friend?',
      answers: ['Mini Mouse', 'Pearl Pureheart', 'Kesha', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'Pearl Pureheart'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is Batmans secret alter ego named?',
      answers: ['Donald Trump', 'Bruce Wayne', 'Don Johnson', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'Bruce Wayne'
    },
    {
      question: 'Al Pratt and Ray Palmer are the civilian identities of what hero?',
      answers: ['Jimmy Neutron', 'The Cell', 'Dr Chemistry', 'The Atom'],
      correctAnswer: 'The Atom'
    },
    {
      question: 'New York Citys Dr. Strange is the "Sorcerer Supreme" when it comes' + 
            ' to defending the earth against magical threats. However what everyday' + 
            ' occupation did he have before he fought super villains?',
      answers: ['neurosurgeon', 'landscaper', 'newspaper reporter', 'computer programmer'],
      correctAnswer: 'neurosurgeon'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the name of the futuristic technology that Iron Man uses to' + 
            ' power his suit?',
      answers: ['Light sabre', 'Arc reactor', 'all of the above', 'none of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'Arc reactor'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which comic character is big, green and you would not want to make him angry?',
      answers: ['Kermit the Frog', 'The Incredible Hulk', 'The Grasshopper', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'The Incredible Hulk'
    },
    {
      question: 'Who portrayed the original Batman on TV',
      answers: ['Michael Keaton ', 'Adam West', 'William Shatner', 'Kevin James'],
      correctAnswer: 'Adam West'
    },
    {
      question: 'The race of warrior tribes called Amazons produced which superheroine' + 
            ' among the following ladies?',
      answers: ['Poison Ivy', 'Wonder Woman', 'Electra', 'Katy Perry'],
      correctAnswer: 'Wonder Woman'
    },
    {
      question: 'Batman protects what city?',
      answers: ['New York City', 'Camden', 'Gotham City', 'Boston'],
      correctAnswer: 'Gotham City'
    },
    {
      question: 'How did Spiderman get his super-powers??',
      answers: ['He was bit by a radioactive spider', 'Ordered on Amazon.com', 
            'A spider laid an egg in his ear', 'None of the above'],
      correctAnswer: 'He was bit by a radioactive spider'
    },
    {
      question: 'What job has Peter Parker, Spider-Mans secret alter ego, traditionally held?',
      answers: ['Painter', 'Stock Trader', 'Writer', 'Photographer'],
      correctAnswer: 'Photographer'
    },
    {
      question: 'Ben Affleck starred in this movie of a super hero in 2003.',
      answers: ['Batman', 'Daredevil', 'Thor', 'Lara Croft Tomb Raider'],
      correctAnswer: 'Daredevil'
    },
    {
      question: 'What are the primary colors of the classic Spider-Man costume?',
      answers: ['Black and White', 'Red and Orange', 'Red and blue', 'Yellow and Green'],
      correctAnswer: 'Red and blue'
    }
  ]
};